

Software Developer seeking roles in Software Development, Configuration Management, Requirement Gathering, Quality Management, Service Delivery, Python, HTML, CSS, XML, Java Script, Tableau, SQL, Power BI



Current Designation: Software Developer Total Experience: 3 Year(s) 0 Month(s)

Current Company: OSI Digital Notice Period: 1 Month

Current Location: Bengaluru / Bangalore Highest Degree: M.Tech [Computers]

Pref. Location: Bengaluru / Bangalore, Chennai, Hyderabad Functional Area: IT Software - Application Programming /

Maintenance

Role: Software Developer

Industry: IT-Software/Software Services

Marital Status: Single/unmarried

Key Skills: Software Developer, Software Development, Configuration Management, Requirement Gathering, Quality

Management, Python, HTML, CSS, XML, Tableau, SQL, Power BI

Verified: Phone Number | Email - id

Last Active: 21-Jan-21 Last Modified: 21-Jan-21

Summary

Almost 3 years of Experience Working as a Tableau Developer.

Having Experience in development of Reports and Dashboard in Tableau.

Creating aggregates, hierarchies, filters, quick filters, calculated measures.

Merge multiple data sources by joining multiple tables and using data blending.

Experience in creating interactive dashboards by using Actions.

By eliminating the unwanted data in worksheets by using filters.

Designed and deployed reports with Drill up and Drop down menu option and

Parameterized and Linked reports using Tableau.

Creating Derived fields using calculated functions and parameters in Tableau

By using context filter improve performance of tableau report.

Designed a report to displaying the Top/Bottom N customers dynamically by using sets and Parameters.

Work Experience

OSI Digital as Software Developer

May 2018 to Till Date

Roles and Responsibilities on working PROJECTS:

Spinal Elements

Duration : Jan2017 - Jul2020 Location of delivery : Tableau Online

Project : Amendia QuickBooks Refresh.

Role : Tableau Developer

Project Description:

Spinal Elements

Spinal Elements is an innovative spine technology company that delivers new standards for spine surgery. Located on campuses in Marietta, Georgia and Carlsbad, California, Spinal Elements is known for its ability to design and bring to market products and procedures that introduce and set new industry standards. We have built a reputation as consistently delivering a New Standard in all dimensions of our company. Our goal is to advance the performance of spinal implants and instruments so that surgeons will have the tools they need to provide the best possible outcomes for their patients.

Responsibilities:

-> To Pull the Data from the QuickBooks and Merge the Data and Upload in to the SQL Server by using DMT tool and run the quires to push he data into tableau and Pushed to Daily Sales Data to Tableau Online and Refresh the Tableau Bridge

-> The Tableau online was refreshed and data is shown up into the repots.

->The Reports sent to the Clients.

Alkermes Inc., USA

Duration: May 2019 ? Till date

Project: ALKERMES Tableau DEV Work

Role: BI Developer **Project Description:**

Alkermes is a leader in innovative medicines that address the unmet needs and challenges of people living with debilitating diseases. As a fully integrated global biopharmaceutical company, Alkermes applies our scientific expertise, proprietary technologies and global resources to develop products that are designed to make a meaningful difference in the way patients manage their disease. All this, combined with our resources and strong global presence, position us as a leading innovator in the global pharmaceutical market, today and for the future. Our work mainly deals with developing and designing Tableau Dashboards based on Requirements.

Responsibilities:

- Development of the Dashboard based on BRD.
- Created reports on Particular Time Period like CR3, CR6, Weekly, Monthly, QTD, YTD.
- Created reports on merging two different products on single dashboard and Visualizations are changed based on filter selection
- Validation of Results in SQL Server Management Studio by writing SQL Query.
- Worked on Enhancements on Designed Dashboards based upon the requirements

Coeur HR Needs

Duration: May 2019 ? Jul 2019 Project: Coeur Data HR Needs

Role: BI Developer Project Description:

Coeur Mining, Inc. is a well-diversified growing precious metals producer with five operations in North America. Coeur?s wholly-owned operations include the Palmarejo gold-silver complex in Mexico, the Rochester silver-gold mine in Nevada, the Kensington gold mine in Alaska, the Wharf gold mine in South Dakota and the Silvertip silver-zinc-lead mine in British Columbia. In addition, the Company has interests in several precious metals exploration projects throughout North America. Coeur?s headquarters are located in Chicago, IL.

Responsibilities:

- Development of the Dashboard based on BRD.
- Created reports on Particular Time Period like CR3, CR6, Weekly, Monthly, QTD, YTD.

Brooks Running

Duration: May 2020 ? Till Date Project: Brooks EDW AMS Support

Role: EDW Consultant **Project Description:**

Brooks Sports, Inc., also known as Brooks running, is an American company that designs and markets high-performance men's and women's running shoes, clothing, and accessories. Headquartered in Seattle, Washington, Brooks products are available in 60 countries worldwide. It is a subsidiary of Berkshire Hathaway.

Responsibilities:

- Monitoring the production environment.
- Debugging the issues and Failures

Education

UG: B.Tech/B.E. (Computers) from Jawaharlal Nehru Technological University (JNTU) in 2013

PG: M.Tech (Computers) from JNTUA in 2016

IT Skills

Skill Name	Version Last Used	Experience
Python		
HTML, CSS, XML		0 Year(s) 0 Month(s)
WINDOWS		

1/22/2021 https://freesearch.naukri.com/preview/printResume?uname=b4871287d4434ede25b4b55e3470702e505e080748450f160415140c0...

SQL
Tableau (All Versions), Micro Strategy
Power BI
MS OFFICE

Languages Known

Language	Proficiency	Read	Write	Speak
ENGLISH	Expert			
TELUGU	Expert			
HINDI	Proficient			

Projects

Project Title: ALKERMES Client: Alkermes Inc

Nature of Employment: Full Time Duration: May 2019 - Till Date Onsite / Offsite: Offsite

Project Details: Alkermes is a leader in innovative medicines that address the unmet needs and challenges of people living with debilitating diseases. As a fully integrated global biopharmaceutical company, Alkermes applies our scientific expertise, proprietary technologies, and global resources to develop products that are designed to make a meaningful difference in the way patients manage their disease. All this, combined with our resources and strong global presence, position us as a leading innovator in the global pharmaceutical market, today and for the future. Our work mainly deals with developing and designing Tableau Dashboards based on Requirements.

Work Authorization

Affirmative Action

Job Type: Permanent Category: General

Physically Challenged: No Employment Status: Full time